[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Speaker 2: Thank you for contacting Pet Smart.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] My name is Lady.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Help me help you.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] Speaker 3: Yeah, somebody went online on my online account and and purchased and made a purchase that I need to cancel because it's fraudulent.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: I'm sorry to hear that.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Okay, help me with that just music.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Can you have your name?
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] 3: Jennifer Murphy.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Thank you.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] And please provide to me your phone number and email.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] 3: Direct the order.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] My phone number is 312-451-7007.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] And my email is jenmurphy44 at hotmail.com.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] Thank you so much.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: How long is the second?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Just a moment.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] 3: Let me open the last it's shipping to an address that I don't know anything about.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Just give music $475 and $87.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] That one, right?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Hold on a second.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Oh, sorry, it's loud.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] 3: No, it there was an order that was it was like $277.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Just give me a second because I can see the order here.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Do you receive any order number on your email?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Oh, no.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Give me a second.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I think I know how to search for it if you need a moment.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] 3: It was, yeah, I have an order number.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] Oh, one one zero six five zero five six eight eight.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Jesus Linda just opened it showing a different loud on my end.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Just give me a second to pull that up again.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] This order is for the total amount.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] It's showing $75.87.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Yeah.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Just showing six dry food and with the same thing.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] 3: Hold on just a second.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] I'm on the phone with customer service.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] I got it.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] Just go ahead.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] I'll meet you.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] Hold on a second.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] I just want to confirm.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Speaker 1: Why is this not I don't want that.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] 3: I want no words.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: I'm just going to search with your email if we have any other transactions or something.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Anything here?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Oh, order.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Here we go.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] 3: Yeah, there was a oh, yeah.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] It's the or yes, you're right.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] It's $75.87.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Thank God.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I'm just getting nervous.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] 3: Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: And you didn't request this, right?
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] 3: No, I did not.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] And I have no idea who the address is that this is shipping to.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Mike, I chose Atlanta.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] 3: Yes, but that's not my.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] I did not place this order.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: I'm gonna let's do something.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I'm gonna need to call this store through cancel this order.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] While I do that, I'm gonna send to you an email to receive your password.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] 3: Oh, I'm not looking at it.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Give me a second.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] 3: Oh, my God, there were more.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Just say you an email for you to receive your password, and I will advise you also to withdraw the password on your email.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Okay, once you have the time.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] And allow me just a moment while I call the store to get this order cancel.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] We work back with you.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Allow me just a minute.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Thank you for calling your neighborhood Pet Smart.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Sorry, that option is not available.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] For hours and location, press one to repeat.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Thank you so much for staying by the line.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] 3: Can you hear me?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Yeah, okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Then as measured to you, I sent to you the email to receive your password.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I have sent to you through the computer to receive the password and your email.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] And I just leave in here for our internal team to double-check the provincial transaction, cancel the serious order, and refund back to your card the amount of the 75 days.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] 3: Will I get an email with the cancellation of the order?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: You will get most likely it will be an email.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I can do the follow-up tomorrow because right now we're about to close.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] 3: Okay, I can do the follow-up tomorrow.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] Thank you very much.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] I appreciate it.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] No worries.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] Have a great evening.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Thank you.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Have a great evening you feel as well.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Take care.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] 3: Bye-bye.
[speaker_SPEAKER_02] Bye-bye.